Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Physical Plant Incinerator and Animal Science Building Records 1994-1998
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Physical Plant Incinerator and Animal Science Building Records
1994-1998
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
UA2000-15
Washington State University. Physical Plant
1 Linear foot of shelf space 1 Box
WSU Physical Plant records regarding the WSU Animal Sciences Building from 1994-1998. Includes administrative files, grounds conditions, cost proposals, and reports.
The WSU Physical Plant was originally known as Buildings and Grounds dating back to at least 1908 when a superintendent was appointed to the department. The department underwent a name change to Buildings and Grounds in the 1960's and a reorganizing in the 80's. The department is responsible for small scale construction and remodeling work around the WSU campus, as well as day to day maintenance.
Administrative files from Physical Plant about the Animal Science building, from 1994-1998. Includes costs of replacing items and item conditions within the Animal Science building, and costs on upgrading waste incinerator and the cost proposal for a new incinerator. Also includes early correspondence regarding draft sites for the WSU Pathological Waste and Solid Waste incinerator, as well as janitorial staff files.
This is an unprocessed collection. Any arrangement reflects either a pre-existing order from the records' creators or previous custodians, or preliminary sorting performed by staff.
Items are in their original order.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This material was transferred to WSU Libraries' MASC by Rick Ward of Facilities on May 19, 2000 and retained as UA2000-15.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Physical Plant -- Records and correspondence
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- Animal Sciences Laboratory Building Building #100
  - Design development phase specifications, (10/21/1994) (Box 1)
  - Executive Report: Design development value engineering (test and screen alternatives), (11/11/1994) (Box 1)
  - Workbook and preliminary idea listing: Design development value engineering (test and screen alternatives), (11/11/1994) (Box 1)
  - Energy conservation report/life cycle cost analysis, rev. 02/28/1995 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
- New Incinerator Building #60
  - Program for the incinerator facility (Box 1)
  - Design development submittal (Box 1)
  - Conceptual design analysis (Box 1)
  - Environmental impact statement for WSU replacement medical waste incinerator (2 volumes) (October, 1996) (Box 1)
  - Trade specifications for WSU incinerator upgrades (September, 1995) (Box 1)
  - Draft of the environmental impact statement for the replacement medical waste incinerator (December, 1995) (Box 1)
  - Draft of the environmental impact statement for the replacement medical waste incinerator (March, 1996) (Box 1)
  - Refractories (2 pamphlets) (Box 1)
  - Draft WSU reasonably available control technology incinerator study (Box 1)
  - WSU opinion of probable costs for pathological and solid waste incinerator (Box 1)
  - Draft WSU site selection study for pathological waste incinerator (Box 1)
  - Incinerator costs proposals (Box 1)
  - Early Correspondence
    - 90% submittal specification 15566 and 15888 (Box 1)
    - Meeting Notes (Box 1)
    - Utilities (Box 1)